# **Alan Abzalkhanuly**

askvizi@bk.ru | GitHub | +7 (778) 488 90-08

## **JAVA DEVELOPER**

I am an intern Java developer with over **1 month of experience** in **Java**. I have some knowledge of popular Back-end frameworks such as **Spring Boot** . I'm developing towards Front-end. I have skills in **HTML, CSS, JavaScript** used frameworks **React**.

I like working with people, I enjoy taking on communication with colleagues, mentoring and with elder mentors whose already has offer from big companies. As well to take active part in development, build processes, mentoring. I like studying English, algorithms and backend development, and all sorts of self-development

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: JavaScript, C++, JavaFrameworks: React.js, Spring BootLibraries: Tailwind, React Router

**Databases** : PostgreSQL

**Dev Tools** : IntelliJ IDEA, Git, Gitlab

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Web DeveloperAugust 2022 – December 2022Basta EducationRemote – Almaty

- Designed and developed dynamic and responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Improved website performance and speed through optimization techniques by 30%
- · GitHub: Basta Education

**Web Developer**Morrison
Aug 2021 – September 2022
Remote – Almaty

- Created website by template to take part in **Hackathon** by Morrison Academy
- · GitHub: Hackathon

## **Backend Developer Intern**

October 2022 - Present

Location: Almaty, Kazakhstan

• Assisted senior Backend developers in the development using **Spring Boot, Go** 

### **EDUCATION**

**Kazakh Britain Technical University** *Bachelor Computer Technology and Software* 

Almaty, Kazakhstan September 2022 – Present